Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject Files, 1918 -- 2005; 1973 -- 2004; MS134.005; 3.45 Linear Feet
  - Citibank/Citigroup Correspondence [Culled from Confidential Tissue Files], 1964 -- 2003; MS134.005.029.00029 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1973; MS134.005.029.00030 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - Citicorp Annual Report [Annotated], 1975; MS134.005.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1975; MS134.005.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1987; MS134.005.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1989; MS134.005.032.00004 (Box 32)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1992; MS134.005.032.00005 (Box 32)
  - Citicorp Annual Report, 1996; MS134.005.032.00006 (Box 32)
  - Citigroup Memorial Press Release: Citigroup Remembers Walter Wriston 1919-2005, MS134.005.032.00007 (Box 32)
  - Condolence Correspondence Received at Walter Wriston's Office, January 20-February 1, 2005; MS134.005.032.00008 (Box 32)
  - Dinner at the River Club, Guest List and Seating Chart, 2005; MS134.005.032.00009 (Box 32)
    After Walter Wriston's Memorial service, guests were invited to a reception at the River Club.
  - Dr. & Mrs. Henry Kissinger, 1993 -- 2004; MS134.005.032.00010 (Box 32)
  - Edward Cardinal Egan Correspondence, September 10-22, 2003; MS134.005.032.00011 (Box 32)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Correspondence [Culled from Confidential Tissue Files], 2000 -- 2004; MS134.005.032.00012 (Box 32)
  - General Correspondence [Culled from Confidential Tissue Files], 1982 -- 2004; MS134.005.032.00013 (Box 32)
  - General Emails, 2003 -- 2004; MS134.005.032.00014 (Box 32)
  - George P. Shultz 75th Birthday Party, November 2-December 4, 1995; MS134.005.032.00015 (Box 32)
  - George P. Shultz and Charlotte Swig Party, 1997; MS134.005.032.00016 (Box 32)
  - George P. Shultz Correspondence, 2000 -- 2004; MS134.005.032.00017 (Box 32)
    Included in this folder is a 1980 List of the Camps and Camp Members and Key to Camp Locations: 1980 Midsummer Encampment-Bohemian Grove.
  - Henry M. Wriston: Book Reviews of Challenge to Freedom by Henry M. Wriston, 1943 -- 1984; MS134.005.032.00018 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Brown Monthly: Henry Merritt Wriston, 1889-1978, MS134.005.032.00019 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Correspondence, 1952 -- 1963; MS134.005.032.00020 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Council on Foreign Relations Press Release for the Resignation of Henry M. Wriston, 1967; MS134.005.032.00021 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Henry Merritt Wriston Grant and Fellowship, 1984 -- 1988; MS134.005.032.00022 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: List of Books written by Henry M. Wriston, 1918 -- 1959; MS134.005.032.00023 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Memorial Service at Brown University, 1978; MS134.005.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Memorial Tribute by the Institute of Paper Chemistry, 1978; MS134.005.032.00025 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Memorial Tribute by the Lawrence University Board of Trustees, 1978; MS134.005.032.00026 (Box 32)
  - Henry M. Wriston: Memorial Tribute by the Meeting of Corporation Members and Spouses of Brown University, 1978; MS134.005.032.00027 (Box 32)
  - ISI [Intercollegiate Studies Institute] - Center for the Study of American Civic Literacy, 2004; MS134.005.033.00001 (Box 33)
  - Luncheon for Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II and His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 1976; MS134.005.033.00002 (Box 33)
  - MUFLG [Municipal Union/Financial Leaders Group] News Clippings, Magazine Articles, Meeting Minutes, 1977 -- 1985; MS134.005.033.00003 (Box 33)
  - Political Correspondence (1 of 2), 1973 -- 1978; MS134.005.033.00004 (Box 33)
  - Political Correspondence (2 of 2), 1979 -- 1984; MS134.005.033.00005 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Holiday Cards from Ronald and Nancy Reagan, 1984 -- 1988; MS134.005.033.00006 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award, 2004; MS134.005.033.00007 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Citigroup Press Release, 2004; MS134.005.033.00008 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Citigroup Reception Honoring Walter B. Wriston, Correspondence, 2004; MS134.005.033.00009 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Citigroup Reception Honoring Walter B. Wriston, Guest List and Invitation, 2004; MS134.005.033.00010 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Congratulatory Calls, 2004; MS134.005.033.00011 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Congratulatory Correspondence, 2004; MS134.005.033.00012 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Congratulatory Correspondence, 2004; MS134.005.033.00013 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Congratulatory Correspondence, 2004; MS134.005.033.00014 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Congratulatory Emails, 2004; MS134.005.033.00015 (Box 33)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Family Correspondence, 2004; MS134.005.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: List of Past Winners, 1993 -- 2003; MS134.005.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: Manhattan Institute for Policy Research Memorandum for Friends & Supporters, 2004; MS134.005.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award: White House and Citigroup Press Releases, 2004; MS134.005.034.00004 (Box 34)
  - Retirement Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984; MS134.005.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Retirement Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984; MS134.005.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Richard Vigilante Correspondence, 1999; MS134.005.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Rose and Milton Friedman Correspondence, 2002; MS134.005.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Take Me Out to the Ballgame, Citicorp/Citibank Brochure, 1990; MS134.005.034.00009 (Box 34)
  - Thank you Correspondence for the Presidential Medal of Freedom Award Reception held by Citigroup at the Links Club, 2004; MS134.005.034.00010 (Box 34)
  - Walter B. Wriston Biographical Information, 2004; MS134.005.034.00011 (Box 34)
  - Walter B. Wriston Chair of International Business Relations at the Fletcher School of Law & Diplomacy, 2003 -- 2004; MS134.005.034.00012 (Box 34)
  - Walter B. Wriston Obituaries, 2005; MS134.005.034.00013 (Box 34)
  - Walter B. Wriston Memorial Service at Christ Church United Methodist Attendees, 2005; MS134.005.034.00014 (Box 34)
  - Walter B. Wriston Timeline by Kurt Willett, 2005; MS134.005.034.00015 (Box 34)
  - White House Correspondence, 1972 -- 1985; MS134.005.034.00016 (Box 34)
  - Who? (Who Else?) by D.V.S., 1984; MS134.005.034.00017 (Box 34)
    This song may have been created for Walter Wriston's retirement party from Citicorp.
  - Writings and Speeches Correspondence [Culled from Confidential Tissue Files], 1989 -- 2003; MS134.005.034.00018 (Box 34)
  - Biowriston71204 [Biography of Walter B. Wriston], 2004; MS134.005.041.00016 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets - Forum Discussion on the Legacy of Walter Wriston], MS134.005.041.00017 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Chair [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00018 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Citigroup Remembers Walter Wriston] itp050124b3, MS134.005.041.00019 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Debt [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00020 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Economics [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00021 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Ex Post Facto [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00022 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Foreign Affairs [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00023 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Foreign Affairs2 [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00024 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Fletcher 1 [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00025 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Fletcher 2 [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00026 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Fletcher 3 [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00027 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Fletcher 4 [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00028 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Guest book from Walter B. Wriston's memorial service, 2005; MS134.005.041.00029 (Box MS134 Shared 5)
  - Guest book from Walter B. Wriston's memorial service, 2005; MS134.005.041.00030 (Box MS134 Shared 5)
  - Incubator [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00031 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Industrial Example [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00032 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Laws [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00033 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Letter to Alan Greenspan] Greenspan, MS134.005.041.00034 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Letter to Julie Suk] FA, MS134.005.041.00035 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Letter to Mark Buchanan] Buchanan71702WBW, MS134.005.041.00036 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Letter to Michele Sindona by Walter Wriston], MS134.005.041.00037 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Letter to President George W. Bush] ThePresident61204, 2004; MS134.005.041.00038 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc. [Memorials] [1 of 5], MS134.005.041.00039 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc. [Memorials] [2 of 5], MS134.005.041.00040 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc. [Memorials] [3 of 5], MS134.005.041.00041 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc. [Memorials- correspondence] [4 of 5], MS134.005.041.00042 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, articles, etc. [Memorials] [5 of 5], MS134.005.041.00043 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Principles vs rules.doc [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00044 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotes, MS134.005.041.00045 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [1 of 7], MS134.005.041.00046 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [2 of 7], MS134.005.041.00047 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [3 of 7], MS134.005.041.00048 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [4 of 7], MS134.005.041.00049 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [5 of 7], MS134.005.041.00050 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [6 of 7], MS134.005.041.00051 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [7 of 7], MS134.005.041.00052 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [1 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00053 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [2 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00054 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [3 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00055 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [4 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00056 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [1 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00057 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [2 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00058 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [3 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00059 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [4 of 4] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00060 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Quotation files [1 of 1] [Speech file], MS134.005.041.00061 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Street Lamp [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00062 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Top20sta.doc [U.S. Employment Data] [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00063 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Untitled [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00064 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Vigilante [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00065 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Walter B. Wriston entry in Scribner's Encyclopedia of American Lives, by Phillip Zweig, includes letter from Zweig], MS134.005.041.00066 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Washibngton [Washington] [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00067 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - WBW letters to Henry M. Wriston (Originals), 1952 -- 1963; MS134.005.041.00068 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - Wealth [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00069 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - [Wesleyan reunion material], 1976 -- 1981; MS134.005.041.00070 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
  - York [Unidentified fragment], MS134.005.041.00071 (Box MS134 Shared 4)
- Photographs, 1925 -- 2004; 1932 -- 1977; MS134.006; 2.2 Linear Feet; 49 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains images of Walter B. Wriston, as well as his family, colleagues, and home in Connecticut from 1925-2004.
  The photographic prints in the collection were created from eight CDs included in the first accession of Wriston material (though not every CD image file has a corresponding print). For each print, the CD name and the file name of the image is listed in the notes field. Some of the images are copyrighted to Harwood Studio, Citicorp/Citigroup, the "New York Times," James Leynse, and Douglas Levere.
  Two prints, one of Walter B. Wriston with President Richard M. Nixon and members of the National Commission on Productivity and one of Walter and Kathryn Wriston with president Jimmy Carter, were received in October 2009 and are housed separately in an oversize box. They do not correspond with images on any CDs.
  The photographic prints in this series are arranged chronologically. CDs are arranged as received.
  - Young Walter B. Wriston and family at Lawrence University, 1925; MS134.006.035.00001; Unknown (Box 35)
    Back Row: Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father) Front Row: Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister); Ruth Bigelow Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's mother); and Walter B. Wriston. Photot taken during Henry Merritt Wriston's presidency at Lawrence University (Appleton, Wisconsin). The image was created from 'File2816' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow
  - Walter B. Wriston at eleven years old in Appleton, Wisconsin, 1931-07; MS134.006.035.00002; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2817' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston at twelve years old in Appleton, Wisconsin, 1932; MS134.006.035.00003 (Box 35)
    The print was created from 'File2810' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514. It is copyrighted to Harwood Studio in Appleton, Wisconsin.
  - Walter B. Wriston seated in lawn chair, 1938; MS134.006.035.00004; Unknown (Box 35)
    This picture was taken a year after Wriston graduated from Appleton High School. The print and digital image were created from 'File2826' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3'.
  - Walter B. Wriston during his tenure as editor of the 'Argosy', 1940; MS134.006.035.00005; Unknown (Box 35)
    'Argosy' was Wesleyan University's student newspaper. Barbara Brengle also pictured. The print and digital image were created from 'File2809' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Barbara Brengle
  - Ruth Bigelow Wriston, 1940; MS134.006.035.00006 (Box 35)
    The print was created from 'File2818' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2' located in MS134.006.036.00002 box number 39090014014514.
    photographic print; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow
  - Walter B. Wriston with his sister, grandmother, and wife, 1943; MS134.006.035.00007; Unknown (Box 35)
    Left to Right: Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister), Jennie Atcheson Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandmother), Walter B. Wriston, and Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife). The print and digital image were created from 'File2807' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Barbara Brengle; Wriston, Jennie Atcheson
  - Henry Merritt Wriston and, his wife, Ruth Bigelow Wriston, 1940; MS134.006.035.00008; Unknown (Box 35)
    These are Walter B. Wriston's parents. The print and digital image were created from 'File2812' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow
  - Henry Lincoln Wriston and his wife, Jennie Atcheson Wriston, 1947; MS134.006.035.00009; Unknown (Box 35)
    Henry Lincoln Wriston and his wife, Jennie Atcheson Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandparents). The print and digital image were created from 'File2811' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Henry Lincoln; Wriston, Jennie Atcheson
  - Henry Lincoln Wriston, Walter B. Wriston and Henry Merritt Wriston, 1942-10; MS134.006.035.00010; Unknown (Box 35)
    Left to Right: Henry Lincoln Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandfather), Walter B. Wriston, and Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father) at Walter B. Wriston's wedding to Barbara Brengle in Scarsdale, New York. Henry Lincoln Wriston performed the marriage ceremony of Walter B. Wriston and Barbara Brengle. The print and digital image were created from 'File2820' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Henry Lincoln; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Henry Merritt
  - Walter B. Wriston in his army uniform, 1944; MS134.006.035.00011; Unknown (Box 35)
    Walter B. Wriston in his army uniform during World War II at his grandparent's (Henry Lincoln Wriston and Jennie Atcheson Wriston) home in Manhattan, NY. The print and digital image were created from 'File2808' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
  - Walter B. Wriston and family at Brown University, 1944; MS134.006.035.00012; Unknown (Box 35)
    Left to Right: Ruth Bigelow Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's mother), Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father), Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister), Walter B. Wriston, and Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife) during Henry Merritt Wriston's presidency at Brown University. The print and digital image were created from 'File2821' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Barbara Brengle
  - Henry Merritt Wriston and Marguerite Woodsworth on their wedding day, 1947-06; MS134.006.035.00013; Unknown (Box 35)
    Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father) on his wedding day to Marguerite Woodsworth. The print and digital image were created from 'File2815' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Woodsworth, Marguerite
  - Barbara Brengle Wriston holding Catherine Wriston, 1948; MS134.006.035.00014; Unknown (Box 35)
    Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife) holding Catherine Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's daughter) winter 1948. The print and digital image were created from 'File2813' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Barbara Brengle; Quintal, Catherine Wriston
  - Walter B. Wriston with his daughter, Catherine, in front of the Statue of Liberty, 1954; MS134.006.035.00015; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2814' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Catherine Wriston
  - Walter B. Wriston in his early years at First National City Bank, 1955; MS134.006.035.00016; Unknown (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The print and digital image were created from 'File2822' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3'
  - Henry Merritt Wriston with a copy of 'Foreign Affairs', 1960; MS134.006.035.00017 (Box 35)
    The print was created from 'File2819' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2' located in MS134.006.036.00002 box number 39090014014514.
    photographic print; Wriston, Henry Merritt
  - President John F. Kennedy shaking hands with Walter B. Wriston, 1963; MS134.006.035.00018; Unknown (Box 35)
    All pictured are members of the Task Force on International Investment. The print and digital image were created from 'File2905' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Kennedy, John F.
  - Walter B. Wriston and Kathryn Dineen on their wedding day, 1968-03; MS134.006.035.00019; Unknown (Box 35)
    Picture taken at St. Ignatius Loyola Roman Catholic Church. Behind the couple are Reverend Robert Haskins and Henry Merritt Wriston, also present is Carolyn B. Dineen Randall (Kathryn Dineen Wriston's sister). This image is copyrighted to the 'New York Times.' The print and digital image were created from 'File2804' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen
  - Walter B. Wriston at Citicorp/Citigroup, 1970; MS134.006.035.00020 (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The print was created from 'File2823' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3' located in MS134.006.036.00003 box number 39090014014514.
    photographic print
  - Walter B. Wriston and daughter Catherine on her wedding day, 1971-08; MS134.006.035.00021; Unknown (Box 35)
    Walter B. Wriston with his daughter, Catherine, on her wedding day to Richard Quintal in the Church of Heavenly Rest (New York, N.Y.). The print and digital image were created from 'File2803' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
  - Walter B. Wriston and Citicorp/Citigroup notables at groundbreaking for Citicorp Center, 1972; MS134.006.035.00022; Unknown (Box 35)
    Thomas Creamer (Citicorp/Citigroup), Walter B. Wriston (Citicorp/Citigroup), and Reverend Ralph E. Peterson (St. Peter's Church) at the groundbreaking for Citicorp Center. This image is copyrighted to Citigroup. The print and digital image were created from 'File2824' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Creamer, Thomas; Peterson, Ralph E.
  - President Richard M. Nixon and members of the National Commission on Productivity, 1974; MS134.006.035.00023; Unknown (Box 35)
    Walter B. Wriston is seated on the left on the far end of the table. Picture taken in The White House Cabinet Room. The print and digital image were created from '07082210450_1' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Nixon, Richard M.
  - Walter B. Wriston on 'Meet the Press', 1975-04; MS134.006.035.00024 (Box 35)
    Left to Right: (Top Row) Arthur M. Wood, Chairman of Sears, Roebuck & Company; Walter B. Wriston, Chairman of Citicorp and First National City Bank; Donald C. Cook, American Electric Power Company, Inc. (Bottom Row) Lawrence E. Spivak, Host; Thomas A. Murphy, Charmian of General Motors Company; Reginald H. Jones, Chairman of General Electric; Irving S. Shapiro, Chairman of E. I. du Pont De Nemours & Company on 'Meet the Press,' April 20. The print was created from 'File2907' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5' located in MS134.006.036.00005 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston and President Gerald R. Ford, 1976; MS134.006.035.00025; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2806' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Ford, Gerald R.
  - Walter B. Wriston at Citicorp/Citigroup, 1985; MS134.006.035.00026; Unknown (Box 35)
    The print and digital image were created from 'File2646' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4'.
  - Seated portrait of Walter B. Wriston, 1980; MS134.006.035.00027; Unknown (Box 35)
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The print and digital image were created from 'File2647' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4'.
  - Walter B. Wriston being sworn in as Chairman of President Ronald Reagan's Economic Advisory Board, 1982; MS134.006.035.00028; Unknown (Box 35)
    Also pictured, George P. Shultz. The print and digital image were created from 'File2805' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1'.
    photographic print; Wriston, Walter B.; Shultz, George P.